ecomexpress.in 2016-02-23

# Ecom-Express

Ecom is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. We believe it is important you know how we treat the information we receive from you, on the Internet. In general, you can visit Ecom on the World Wide Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. When information is needed, we shall let you know, at the time of collection, the purpose of collecting such information. Usually, we require this information to better understand your needs and provide you with a more customised service.

We shall not retain the information for longer than it is required. We do not collect your "sensitive personal data or information" as defined under the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011 and we strongly urge you not to disclose such information on this site or share such information with other users through this site. When submitting your personal information to us, you represent to us that such information is true, accurate and current in all respects, and you grant your unconditional consent to the collection, storage and use of your personal information. You may review the information provided by you at all times and also update the same to ensure that it is accurate. No representations, warranties or guarantees whatsoever are made by us for the accuracy, adequacy, reliability, completeness of any information provided by you. 

This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and/or alteration of information under our control. The data resides behind a firewall, with access restricted to authorized Ecom personnel. Though all measures have been taken to ensure the safety and security of your information you will appreciate that there could be instances beyond our control which could result in unwarranted disclosure of your personal information and you fully understand the risks associated with disclosure of personal information on such forum. 

You recognize and understand that there is no compulsion on you to provide us with your personal information and any and all personal information provided by you to us is with your full consent, own volition and desire to provide such personal information. 

You hereby consent to your information being disclosed to a third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure or to comply with any applicable law and transfer of such information for certain commercial or business purposes. If you object to your information being transferred or used in the manner as provided herein, please do not use the site. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can get in touch at **info@ecomexpress.in**

Ecom web site may contain links to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites. Users of this site who link to other sites through this site should read the privacy policy and terms of use of such sites before using the services on such sites. 

From time to time, we may revise this privacy policy to reflect initiatives, changes in the law or technology or changes in our practices regarding the collection and use of personal information. Please check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.

The access and use of this site is provided to you on the condition that you accept all the terms and conditions contained herein in their entirety without modifications or reservation of any kind.  
**Note:** **_IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ANY OF THE FOREGOING TERMS AND CONDITIONS OR ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THIS SITE._**
